(Sheldon:)but good job, Howard!
(Howard:)Thanks. Our culprit
is one Mr. Todd Zarnecki, 2711
(Howard:)Ocean View Road,
(Howard:)Carlsbad, California.
(Sheldon:)The name and the address
drip with evil.
(Raj:)What else do we know about him?
Why, quite a
bit, actually.
(Leonard:)I'll bet he's some loser
who lives with his parents.
(Howard:)Yes, he does live
with his parents.
(Howard:)Here's a Google Earth
shot of their house.
(Sheldon:)Excellent!
It's in a cul-de-sac.
(Sheldon:)We can box him in.
(Leonard:)Hold on, you're thinking
of going there?
(Sheldon:)Carlsbad is only
a couple of hours away.
(Policeman:)Fine.
(Leonard:)You walk up to the house,
knock on the door
(Leonard:)and demand your stuff back.
What if he says no?
(Sheldon:)I don't know if you've been
following the news, Leonard,
(Sheldon:)but there have been
some terrific advancements
(Sheldon:)in the field of torture.
(Leonard:)No one's getting tortured.
(Sheldon:)Fine, we'll abide by
the Geneva Convention.
But ask yourself this:
(Sheldon:)in the course
of our lives,